miamastore.com 2014-05-06

# Privacy policy - MiamaStore.com

**PRIVACY NOTICE**

We collect information from Site users in several different ways, with the goal of providing an efficient, meaningful, and customized shopping experience. For example, we can use your personal information to:   
   * Record and quickly bring up information you’ve given previously  
   * Help you quickly find information, products, and services  
   * Create content that is relevant to you  
   * Alert you of our new information, products, and services

**Registration and Ordering:** In order to use certain parts of this Site or order products, all customers must fill out an online registration form with personal information, including but not limited to, your name, gender, shipping and billing address(es), phone number and email address. In addition, we may ask for your country of residence and/or your organization's country of operation, so that we can comply with applicable laws and regulations. This information is used for billing, order processing and internal marketing as well as to communicate with you about your order and our site. ****

**Log Files:** Like most websites, the Site server automatically recognizes the Internet URL from which you access this Site. We may also log your Internet protocol (IP) address, Internet service provider, and date/time stamp for system administration, order verification, internal marketing and system troubleshooting purposes. (An IP address may indicate the location of your computer on the Internet.)  **    **

Any electronic image on the Site, such as an ad banner, can function as a web beacon. We may use content or ads from third-party advertising companies that may use cookies and web beacons to measure web page visits or amount of products purchased.   
**Any information these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any personal information we collect.

How does MiamaStore.com use my personal information?

**

** Internal Use:** We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may use your personal information internally to collect general information about visitors to this Site, improve Site content and layout, improve our outreach, and market our services and products.

**Communication with You:** We will use your personal information to communicate with you about our Site and your orders. All customers must provide an email address to allow communication with MiamaStore.com regarding orders placed.

**Does MiamaStore.com ever give out my personal information?**

We sell merchandise, not information **— We do not sell, rent, trade, license, or otherwise disclose your personal or financial information to anyone, except in the following specific situations:

     Third-party service providers:

** Like most catalog and Internet wholesalers, we sometimes use third-party service providers to perform specific functions on our behalf. Any information disclosed to them is solely to help in their provision of service. For example, we provide your name, shipping address, email and phone number to partners such as DHL and FEDEX in order to guarantee delivery of your orders, and we may use relevant customer information in order to monitor the quality of the third party’s service.  
Similarly, we must provide your credit card number to financial services organizations such as credit card processors and issuers in order to process payments. We protect all submissions of your credit card number for authorization with state-of-the-art data encryption. 

**Legal requirement to disclose information:** We may be required to disclose information if subpoenaed, served with a court order or requested by law-enforcement officials conducting investigations, or if we are otherwise required by law to disclose such information. We will also release personal information when necessary to protect our legal rights or enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud, or to prevent fraud by users who attempt fraud or other illegal activity on our Site.  
**  
Merger and/or sale of assets:** We do not sell, trade or rent personal information   
to other companies in the course of our business.   
**  
Non-personally identifiable information:** We may share information that does not identify you or any user, such as the number of daily visitors to a particular page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date, with third parties such as advertising partners.

 **How does MiamaStore.com secure information collected about me?** ****

This Site incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as:  
     * Safeguarding all financial transactions done through this Site with Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") encryption   
     * Granting only employees who are providing a specific service access to your personal information   
     * Working only with third-party service providers who we believe adequately secure all computer hardware.

 **Are children allowed to use MiamaStore.com?**

We respect children's privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 18. Elsewhere on this Site, you have represented and warranted that you are either 18 years of age or are using the Site with the supervision of a parent or guardian.  
If you are under the age of 18, please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you when using the Site.

 **How does MiamaStore.com use and disclose information collected from me offline?** ****

As MiamaStore.com collects most information through our Site, this Privacy Policy applies only to online collection of personal information.  
We also protect all personal information that is collected from you offline, such as through phone calls. If we contact you by telephone regarding an order or payment, we will ask only for the personal information needed to place your order or resolve your issue. When we need to store information related to an order, we enter it into our database through SSL encryption.

 **MIAMASTORE DO NOT COLLECT ANY INFORMATION ABOUT YOUR CREDIT CARD!**

This Policy does not attempt to cover all possible offline methods of collecting or using personal information, however, we will treat any offline collection, use, or disclosure of personal information in a manner consistent with our online practices.

Please [contact us](http://www.miamastore.com/contact-form.php) with any questions about our Privacy Notice.
